This is a Doom "Competition" .LMP - Please forward it

IWAD: DOOM2.wad
PWAD: AV.wad (Second Release)
Map: 17
Map title: Nukefall
Skill level: Ultra-Violence
Category: UV -respawn

Kills - 101%
Items - 100%
Secrets - 100%
and a time of 04:08
Date Achieved - Wednesday, 30th August 2017 at 14:21

Runner: Jakub Puk
Nickname: Huncd6814
Country: United Kingdom
Email: kuba27131@gmail.com 

Demo was recorded using DOOM2 v1.9 through DOSBox 0.74 (doom2.exe -file AV.wad -playdemo ar17-408) 

Information:
The map was incredibly tough on -respawn, and you have to be incredibly lucky throughout the map while you're playing it due to the sheer number of respawning enemies that can appear. My strategy was also to use the BFG on the Chaingunners after taking the teleporter from the secret in order to log enough kills because my strategy was to avoid killing the Arch-Viles at the very end of the map. 

The revenant section was very hard as the Imps can distract you down the corridor by catching you offguard. The revenants can also respawn any second. 

Took me close to 300 failed attempts just to achieve this run. I was going to go for a sub-four minute run, but the sheer difficulty meant that I had to increase that target to under 4:15. 